Contact

rsim64@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rondasimpson-msn-rn-ccm-77822237 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Healthcare Hospitals

Honors-Awards

Honors Society of Nursing

Ronda Simpson, MSN,RN,CCM

Senior Staff Nurse | Field Case Manager | Nurse Manager | Valdosta, Georgia

Summary

Registered Nurse with more than 15 years of experience of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Education, Medical-Surgical, Hemodialysis, Interventional Radiology, Surgical Services, Hospice, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Cardiac Intensive Care, Utilization Management, Case Management, HEDIS and STARS measures and quality improvement.

Strong healthcare services professional with a MSN focused in Leadership and Management from Western Governors University.

Experience

UnitedHealth Group 3 years 11 months Clinical Claims Review RN June 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months) Remote

RN Case Manager September 2016 - Present (3 years 11 months) Valdosta/Tifton

United States Air Force
Utilization Manager
November 2015 - Present (4 years 9 months)
Moody AFB

Hospice of South Georgia & Langdale Hospice House RN Case Manager
April 2012 - September 2015 (3 years 6 months)

South Georgia Medical Center

8 years 3 months

OR Circulator-RN August 2011 - August 2012 (1 year 1 month)

Interventional Radiology and Cardiac Progressive Unit-RN June 2004 - August 2011 (7 years 3 months)

Hemodialysis-RN November 2005 - August 2008 (2 years 10 months)

Education

Western Governors University

MSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2015 - 2017)